heatnation.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Heat Nation knows that you care about how your personal information is used and  
shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following  
to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are  
accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Heat Nation’s treatment of personal information that  
Heat Nation gathers when you are on the Heat Nation website and when you use  
Heat Nation services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third  
parties that Heat Nation does not own or control, or to individuals that  
Heat Nation does not employ or manage.

Information Collected by Heat Nation

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our  
website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and  
efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is  
incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of  
information from our Heat Nation users:

1\. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you  
enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not  
to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to  
take advantage of many of our special features.

2\. Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact  
with us. Heat Nation and its authorized agents automatically receive and record  
certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including  
your IP address, Heat Nation cookie information, and the page you requested.  
Heat Nation uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers,  
analyze trends and administer the website.  
o Heat Nation may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page  
has been viewed.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously.  
While Heat Nation will not be able to provide you with a personalized  
experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these  
programs are available.

E-mail Communications  
Heat Nation is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your  
email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as  
detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. Heat Nation may send  
out e-mails with Heat Nation-related news, products, offers, surveys or  
promotions.

Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s  
hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your  
browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by  
how many people. Heat Nation cookies do not collect personal information, and  
we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal  
information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail  
address is.

The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct  
you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to  
command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to  
fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated  
because cookies allow you to use some of Heat Nation’s coolest features.

Heat Nation’s advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that  
makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable  
information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If  
you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our  
advertising partner Platform-A’s privacy policy and opt-out page.

Sharing Your Information

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to  
anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described  
below.

Heat Nation Personnel: Heat Nation personnel and authorized consultants and/or  
contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal  
course of Heat Nation business.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In  
these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the  
business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Heat Nation, or substantially  
all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the  
assets that is transferred.

Protection of Heat Nation and Others: We may release personal information when  
we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to  
enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the  
rights, property, or safety of Heat Nation, our employees, our users, or  
others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and  
organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Syndication: Heat Nation allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public  
content within the Heat Nation website.

With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your  
personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose  
incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and  
you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.

Children Under 18 Years of Age

You must be 13 years and older to register to use the Heat Nation website. As a  
result, Heat Nation does not specifically collect information about children.  
If we learn that Heat Nation has collected information from a child under the  
age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We  
recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their  
parents’ permission before using Heat Nation or sending information about  
themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Heat Nation may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole  
discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to thePrivacy  
Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes  
to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the  
Heat Nation website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how  
we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit the Heat Nation website, your visit and any possible dispute  
over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use,  
including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application  
of California state law.

Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 26, 2014 and last  
updated May 21, 2014.

 **Advertising Privacy Statement**

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at support@heatnation.com and contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)
